Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Firemen and Oilers 1920-1925 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Firemen and Oilers, 1940 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Firemen and Oilers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Firemen and Oilers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Firemen and Oilers 1955-1959 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Firemen and Oilers '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Firemen and Oilers 1960-1964 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Firemen and Oilers, International Brhd 1960-1969 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Firemen and Oiler 1970 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Flight Attendants, Assoc. of, 1974-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Flight Engineers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Flight Engineers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Flight Engineers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Flight Engineers 1965-1969 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Flight Engineers International Assoc., 1970-1977 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Flight Radio Officers, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Food, Tobacco '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Food, Tobacco '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers Union, 1961-1963 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- United Food And Commercial Workers International Union (AFL-CIO), 1980-1986 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Food Workers District Union, Allied, 1964-1967 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Foreman's Assn. '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Foremens Ass'n. '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Foundry and Metal '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Fur and Leather Worker's '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Fur and Leather '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Fur, Leathers Workers Union '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- International Fur Workers, 1934-1938 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- International Fur Workers Union, 1926-1939 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Furniture Workers of America, United Agreements '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Furniture Workers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Furniture Workers of Am., United (CIO) '50-'59, 1950-1959 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Furniture Workers of America '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Furniture Workers 1965-1969 (Box 92, Folder 13)
- Garment Workers, International Ladies' 1913-1939 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Garment Workers Union, international Ladies Agreements '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Garments -Ladies, 1947-1951 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- International Ladies Garments Workers Union, 1950-1959 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Garments, Ladies '50-'55, 1950-1955 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1950-1955 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, 1950-1954 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers Unions, 1959-1962 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Association of Piped Buttonhole Manufacturers, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Garment Workers, Ladies, 1955-1960 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Garment Workers, Ladies '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1954-1959 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Garment Workers' Union, 1955-1967 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Garment Workers Union, International Ladies' Agreements, 1950-1965 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Garment Workers, 1950-1967 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Garment Workers Union, 1960-1972 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Garment Workers Union, 1960-1963 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Garment Workers, International Ladies '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Garment Workers International Ladies', 1957-1972 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- ILGWU, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- ILGWU 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- International Garment Ladies Workers Union, 1976-1979 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1969-1976 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- ILGWU 1977- (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Garment Workers, United '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Garment Workers, United '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Garment Workers, United 1955-1959 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers '40-'45, 1940-1945 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers, 1946-1949 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers, 1946-1948 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers, 1945-1949 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Gas, Coke and Chemical '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, C.I.O., 1950-1954 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Agreement, 1950-1954 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Agreements United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, 1950-1954 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Gas, Coke and Chemical '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Agreements - United Chemical Workers of America, 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Agreements - United Chemical Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Agreements - United Chemical Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Agreements - United Chemical Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Gas, Coke, Chemical Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Gas, coke, and Chemical '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Gas Workers Union, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Glass Bottle Blowers, 1918-1939 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Glass Bottle Blowers 1940-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of U.S. can Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Glass Bottle Blowers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Glass Bottle Blowers 1965-1969 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Glass, Ceramic and Silica Sand Workers, Fed. Of Agreements '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Glass, Ceramic and Silica Sand 1945-1949 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Glass, Ceramic and Silica Sand '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Glass and Ceramic Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1955-1963 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Glass and Ceramic Workers, United, 1955-1959 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Glass and Ceramic Workers of N.A., 1960-1964 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Glass and Ceramic Workers, United 1965-69, 1965-1969 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- United Glass and Ceramic Workers 1970-1975 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Glass and Ceramic Workers of N.A., United, 1968-1976 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Glass Cutters, 1949 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Glass Cutter, Window '50-'55, 1950-1955 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- Glass Cutters, Window 1955-1959 (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers International Union, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Glass, Pottery, Plastics, and Allied Workers '84-'87, 1984-1987 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- Glass Workers Union of N.A. Am. Flint, 1942 (Box 102, Folder 12)
- Glass Workers Union of N.A., Agreements, 1945-1949 (Box 102, Folder 13)
- Glass Workers, American Flint, 1950-1954 (Box 102, Folder 14)
- Glass Workers, Am. Flint '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Glass Workers, Am. Flint '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Glass Workers, American Flint 1965-1969 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Glass Workers, Nat'l Windows 1919-1923 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Glove Cutters and Shavers Unions '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Glove Workers' Union '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Glove Workers' Union '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Glove Workers of America '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Glove Workers, United 1965-1969 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- Gov't Employees American Fed. 1962-78, 1962-1978 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Gov't and Civic and Civic Employees '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Gov't and Civic Employees 1955-1956 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Graphic Arts International Union Agreements, 1970-1973 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- Grain Millers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- Grain Millers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Grain Miller '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Grain Millers. American Federation, 1960-1962 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Grain Millers, American Federation of Agreements '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Grain Miller 1970- (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Grain Processor, Amer. Fed. Of, 1941-1943 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Granite Cutters' '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Granite Cutters '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Granite Cutters International Association, 1960-1964 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Granite Cutters 1966-1969 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Graphic Arts International Union, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Guards Union, International 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Guards Union, International 1955-1959 (Box 105, Folder 8)
- Guards Union, International 1960-1969 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Guard Workers of N.A. Indep. Plant '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 105, Folder 10)
- Guard Workers of NA, Plant (Ind.) 1961 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Guard Workers, United Plant 1949 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Guard Workers, United Plant '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- Guard Workers, United Plant 1955-1959 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- Guard Workers, United Plant 1960-64, 1960-1964 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Guard Workers, United Plant 1965-1969 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- Guard Workers, United Plant 1965-1969 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Guard Workers - United Plant 1970-75, 1970-1975 (Box 105, Folder 18)
- Handbag, Belt, Luggage '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- Handbag, Luggage, Belt '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- Hatters, Cap and Millinery, 1930-1934 (Box 105, Folder 21)
- Hatters, Cap and Millinery Wkrs. '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 105, Folder 22)
- Hatters, Cap '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 105, Folder 23)
- Hatters '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 24)
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery, 1937-1940 (Box 105, Folder 25)
- Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 105, Folder 26)
- Hatters, Cap and Millinery 1960-1964 (Box 105, Folder 27)
- Hatters, Cap and Millinery 1960-64, 1960-1964 (Box 105, Folder 28)
- Hatters, Cap and Millinery 1965-1969 (Box 105, Folder 29)
- Hockey League Players Assoc., 1981-1988 (Box 105, Folder 30)
- Hod Carriers, Bldg. and Common Labor Union '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Hod Carriers and Building Laborers E 1900-1940 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Hod Carriers, 1940-1944 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Hod Carriers, 1956 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Hod Carriers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Hod Carriers, 1964-1966 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Hod Carriers, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Hod Carriers 1960-1964 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Hos Carriers 1965-1969 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Hosiery Workers, 1937-1944 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Hosiery Workers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Hosiery Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Hosiery Workers 1955-1960 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Hotel a Motel Trades Council 1966 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Hotel and Restaurant Emp., 1944-1953 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Intl. Union, 1946-1949 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Hotel and Restaurant Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Intl. Union '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1961-1966 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1964-1966 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Hotel and Restaurant 1965-1970 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Industrial Trades Union 40-44, 1940-1944 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Industrial Trade Union, 1945-1949 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Industrial Workers, Allied, 1958-1962 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Industrial Workers. Allied, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Insurance, Agents Council, 1945-1949 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Industrial Ordinary Insurance Agents Union, 1941-1945 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- International Ass. Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Insurance Agents, 1950-1954 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Insurance Agents' Inter. Union, 1955-1959 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Insurance Agents, Life, 1955-1959 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Insurance Workers of Am., 1950-1954 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Insurance Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Insurance Agents, International Union of Life Agreement, 1960-1964 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Internal Revenue Employees National Association, 1965-1969 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Iron Workers, International Association, 1940-1944 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Iron Workers, International Association of Bridge Structural, and Ornamental Agreement, 1945-1949 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Iron Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Iron Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Iron Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Iron Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Iron Workers, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Isetan, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Jewelry Workers, 1945-1949 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Jewelry Workers, International, 1950-1954 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Jewelry, 1955-1959 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Jewelry Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Jewelry Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Knitgood Workers Union, 1963 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Laborers and Pre-1964, 1960-1963 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Laborers Inter. Union, 1962-1968 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Laborer's International Union, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Laborer's Protective Union (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Lace Operatives Amalgamated, 1955-1968 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Lathers, 1918-1954 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Lathers, 1955-1959 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Lathers International Union. Wood, Wire and Metal, 1960-1964 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Lathers International Union, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Laundry Workers, 1940-1947 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Laundry Workers, 1950-1967 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Leather Workers, International Union, 1946-1959 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Leather Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Leather Workers, 1965-1968 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Letter Carriers, National Association of 1964- (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Letter Carrier National, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Lithpgraphers, 1950-1954 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Lithographers, 1955-1959 (Box 112, Folder 11)
- Lithographers and Photo Engravers, 1965-1969 (Box 112, Folder 12)
- Lithographers, 1956-1958 (Box 112, Folder 13)
- Lithographers of America, Amalg., 1960-1969 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Lithographers of America, Amal. -CIO Agreement, 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, 1971-1983 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Locomotive Engineers, 1923-1944 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Agreements, 1945-1949 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1953-1959 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Locomotive Engineers, 1957-1971 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Locomotive Engineers, 1950-1954 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- Longshoremen's, 1920-1949 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Longshoremen, 1950-1954 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- Longshoremen's Association International, 1955-1959 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Longshoremen's (ILA), 1960-1964 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- International Longshoreman's Association, 1965-1968 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Longshoremen, International, 1970-1977 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's International Agreements, 1940-1944 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's, 1945-1949 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Longshoremen, Warehouse, 1950-1954 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Longshoremen International Bro. of Warehousemen, 1955-1959 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 1965-1969 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Longshoremen Warehouse, 1970-1975 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 1960-1964 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union International, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Machinists, International Association, 1916-1939 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Machinists, 1940-1945 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists - Agreements, 1947-1950 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Machinists, 1945-1949 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Machinists, 1945-1949 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Machinists, 1945-1949 (Box 116, Folder 6)
- I.A.M., 1953-1959 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- I.A.M., 1950-1954 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- I.A.M., 1950-1954 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists, 1950-1954 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1949-1954 (Box 117, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists, 1954-1959 (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Machinists, 1950-1954 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- I.A.M., 1958-1962 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists, 1950-1954 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- I.A.M., 1955-1959 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1955-1959 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists, 1956-1961 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists, 1955-1961 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists, 1950-1969 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists, 1950-1969 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1955-1969 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists, 1957-1965 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- International Association of Machinists, 1954-1967 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- International Association of Machinists, 1956-1959 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists, 1957-1960 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists, 1955-1959 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Machinists, International Association, 1957-1960 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Machinists, International Association, 1955-1959 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Machinists, International Association, 1955-1959 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists, 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Machinists, International Assoc., 1955-1959 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists, 1958-1962 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1964 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- I.A.M., 1960-1964 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- I.A.M., 1960-1964 (Box 122, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1964 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists, 1961-1969 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists, 1961-1964 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1964 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1969 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1961-1964 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1964 (Box 123, Folder 6)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1965 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1964 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists, 1963 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1964 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1964 (Box 124, Folder 5)
- Machinist, International Association, 1960-1964 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1969 (Box 125, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1969 (Box 125, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1969 (Box 125, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1972 (Box 125, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1972 (Box 125, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists, 1967 (Box 125, Folder 6)
- I.A.M., 1967-1970 (Box 125, Folder 7)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1972 (Box 125, Folder 8)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1996 (Box 126, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists, 1965-1992 (Box 126, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists, 1969-1982 (Box 126, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists, 1970-1986 (Box 126, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists, 1970-1986 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- Machinists 1970-, 1970-1990 (Box 126, Folder 6)
- Machinists, International Association, 1965-1974 (Box 126, Folder 7)
- Mailers Union, Inter., 1965-1974 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- N.Y. Mailers' Union #6, 1965-1967 (Box 127, Folder 2)
- Maintenance Service Employees, 1946 (Box 127, Folder 3)
- Maintenance of Way, 1922-1949 (Box 127, Folder 4)
- Maintenance of Way, 1950-1954 (Box 127, Folder 5)
- Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood of, 1955-1969 (Box 127, Folder 6)
- BMWE - 1970-75, 1970-1975 (Box 127, Folder 7)
- Marble, 1952-1959 (Box 127, Folder 8)
- Marble, 1961-1964 (Box 127, Folder 9)
- Marine Eng. Beneficial Assn., 1944 (Box 127, Folder 10)
- Marine Engineers' Beneficial, 1945-1949 (Box 127, Folder 11)
- Marine Engineers, 1950-1954 (Box 127, Folder 12)
- Marine Engineers' Benefits, 1955-1959 (Box 127, Folder 13)
- MEBA, 1960-1964 (Box 127, Folder 14)
- MEBA, 1965-1969 (Box 127, Folder 15)
- Marine Engineers Beneficial, 1960-1974 (Box 127, Folder 16)
- Marine and Machinists, 1950-1974 (Box 127, Folder 17)
- Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Ind. Union Agreements, 1939-1944 (Box 127, Folder 18)
- Marine and Shipbuilding, 1945-1949 (Box 127, Folder 19)
- Marine, Shipbuilding, 1950-1954 (Box 128, Folder 1)
- Marine and Shipbuilding, 1955-1959 (Box 128, Folder 2)
- Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of Am. Ind. Union Agreements, 1960-1964 (Box 128, Folder 3)
- Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of Am. Ind. Union Agreement, 1965-1969 (Box 128, Folder 4)
- Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of Am, Ind. Union, 1970-1989 (Box 128, Folder 5)
- Maritime, 1938-1944 (Box 128, Folder 6)
- Maritime, 1945-1949 (Box 128, Folder 7)
- International Association of Machinists, 1966-2002 (Box 128, Folder 8)
- Maritime Union, National, 1950-1954 (Box 129, Folder 1)
- Maritime Union, 1950-1954 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- Maritime Union, 1950-1954 (Box 129, Folder 3)
- Maritime Union, 1950-1954 (Box 129, Folder 4)
- Maritime, 1955-1959 (Box 129, Folder 5)
- National Maritime Union, 1955-1956 (Box 129, Folder 6)
- National Maritime Union, 1956 (Box 129, Folder 7)
- Maritime Union, 1955-1959 (Box 129, Folder 8)
- Maritime Union, National, 1955-1959 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Maritime Union, Am. National (cont.), 1955-1959 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- Maritime Union, National, 1955-1959 (Box 130, Folder 3)
- Maritime Union, National, 1955-1959 (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Maritime Union, National, 1955-1959 (Box 130, Folder 5)
- Maritime Union, National, 1955-1959 (Box 130, Folder 6)
- Maritime Union National, 1960-1964 (Box 130, Folder 7)
- United Mine Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 130, Folder 8)
- Maritime Union, International, 1964-1970 (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Maritime Union, International, 1960-1970 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Maritime Union, International, 1963-1964 (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Maritime Union, International, 1961-1964 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Maritime Union, National, 1959-1962 (Box 131, Folder 5)
- Maritime Union, National, 1962-1963 (Box 131, Folder 6)
- Maritime Union, National, 1960-1961 (Box 131, Folder 7)
- Maritime Union, National, 1960-1964 (Box 131, Folder 8)
- 1970 Maritime (Box 131, Folder 9)
- Masters, Mates, 1940-1944 (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Masters, Mates, 1945-1949 (Box 132, Folder 2)
- Masters, Mates, Pilots, 1950-1954 (Box 132, Folder 3)
- Masters, Mates, Pilots, 1955-1959 (Box 132, Folder 4)
- Masters, Mates, Pilots, 1960-1964 (Box 132, Folder 5)
- Masters, Mates, Pilots, 1965-1969 (Box 132, Folder 6)
- Meat Cutters, 1940-1944 (Box 132, Folder 7)
- Meat Cutters, 1945-1949 (Box 132, Folder 8)
- Meat Cutters, 1950-1954 (Box 132, Folder 9)
- Meat Cutters, 1950-1954 (Box 132, Folder 10)
- Meat Cutters and Butchers Union, 1957-1960 (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Meat Cutters and Butchers Union, 1955-1959 (Box 133, Folder 2)
- Meat Cutters and Butchers Union, 1955-1959 (Box 133, Folder 3)
- Meat Cutters and Butchers Union, 1955-1959 (Box 133, Folder 4)
- Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of N.A. Amal. Agreements, 1955-1959 (Box 133, Folder 5)
- Meat Cutters and Butchers Union, 1955-1959 (Box 133, Folder 6)
- Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of N.A., 1964-1967 (Box 133, Folder 7)
- I.A.M. and Maritime Union, 1950-1988 (Box 133, Folder 8)